For sports fans, there’s nothing better than watching a live event on TV or at a sports venue.
对于体育迷而言，没有什么比在电视上或体育场馆里观看现场赛事更过瘾的事了。
But there’s nothing worse than that event being called off because of bad weather.
但最让人扫兴的，莫过于赛事因恶劣天气而取消。
Bad light, a waterlogged pitch or excessive heat can cause matches to be postponed.
光线不足、场地积水或是酷热天气，都可能导致比赛延期。
But according to the latest research, extreme weather might be disrupting the sporting calendar more than ever in the future.
不过最新研究表明，未来极端天气对体育赛事日程的干扰可能会达到前所未有的程度。
In one sport, golf, major tournaments like The Open, are already predicted to be victims of our changing climate.
在高尔夫这项运动中，像英国公开赛这样的大型赛事，就被预测会成为气候变化的受害者。
In the UK, an organisation called The Climate Coalition says that golf courses such as St Andrews could be under water by the end of the century if sea levels rise even slightly.
英国一家名为“气候联盟”的组织表示，哪怕海平面只是小幅上升，圣安德鲁斯这样的高尔夫球场到本世纪末也可能会被淹没。
It told the BBC that its research predicts "cancelled football matches, flooded cricket grounds and golf courses crumbling into the sea."
该组织向英国广播公司透露，其研究预测未来会出现“足球比赛取消、板球场被淹、高尔夫球场坍塌入海”的景象。
The threat to sporting fixtures from climate change has been further highlighted in a new report, commissioned by the Rapid Transition Alliance.
一份由快速转型联盟委托撰写的新报告，进一步强调了气候变化对体育赛事的威胁。
Writing about this for the BBC, Matt McGrath says that "By 2050, it's estimated that almost one in four English football league grounds can expect flooding every year."
马特·麦格拉思在为英国广播公司撰写的相关文章中表示：“据估计，到2050年，英格兰足球联赛将近四分之一的场地每年都会遭遇洪水侵袭。”
This will mean fewer matches played, less opportunity to watch the beautiful game and reduced revenue from ticket sales.
这意味着比赛场次会减少，球迷观看这项精彩运动的机会会变少，门票销售收入也会随之下降。
Cricket also faces huge challenges globally as temperatures rise in places like India, Australia and the West Indies.
随着印度、澳大利亚、西印度群岛等地的气温不断攀升，板球运动在全球范围内也面临着巨大挑战。
The report says that stadiums in Adelaide and Perth will see a 60% increase in days with temperatures over 40℃ over the next decade.
该报告指出，未来十年间，阿德莱德和珀斯的体育场馆，气温超过40摄氏度的天数将会增加60%。
Of course, we know that the solution lies with reducing our carbon footprint.
当然，我们都知道解决之道在于减少碳足迹。
We could travel less to attend sports events, and reduce our waste when we do go.
我们可以减少前往现场观赛的出行次数，即便去观赛，也要减少产生的垃圾。
But this latest report finds that sports leaders are generally failing to address the issue seriously.
但这份最新报告发现，体育界的领导者们普遍没有认真对待这个问题。
However, because sport is universally popular and can be very influential, maybe it should be players, teams and their sponsors who promote a carbon-neutral message to help protect sporting venues - before it’s ‘game over’.
不过，体育运动拥有全球性的受众，影响力不容小觑。或许，应该由运动员、球队及其赞助商来宣扬碳中和理念，助力保护体育场馆——以免为时已晚，落得“赛事终结”的下场。